

COVER LETTER

Dear Hiring Manager's,

I am writing this letter to express my interest in the graphic designer opening as advertised on Indeed.

Life is full of challenges. The process of taking on a challenge is a critical influence on what I partake in life. Every price of my artwork I have completed was an opportunity given to me. I had taken every challenge as an opportunity to diversify my skills to bring it to the next level. As well as being an independent worker, I would love to contribute my idea to an environment that recognizes teamwork.

The fundamental answer to facing a challenge is simplicity. I was influenced by my past experiences when I was growing up in Taiwan.

I moved to Southern California with my wife in 2015, and in 2018, I moved to Las Vegas, and I stopped designing and challenged different industry the supermarket manager.

But I still like to design work. My background from a gaming company and I started on the web and graphic design with over 17 years of experience. And before coming to the US worked a lot of gaming companies many years. My true found passion for art was the answer to my career. As challenging is it to be a native Taiwanese immigrating here, I firmly believe that my artwork in a portfolio will catch your eye. I promise you that it will not be your average portfolio.

Please following are highlights of my skills and accomplishments:

- · Experience in designing advertisements, catalogs, etc
- · Ability to bring a fresh perspective to the brand without losing original intent
- · Excellent communication skills and ability to interact with clients and understand their requirements
- · Excellent team player and ability to work in groups to complete the desired task

Advantage

- · Time Management Skills, manage up to 5 projects or tasks at a given time while under pressure to meet strict weekly deadlines
- · Complete tasks very quickly and accurately
- · Still improving steadily in my role and challenges
- · Planning and strategic thinking
- · Problem-solving and decision-making
- · Communication and teamwork

Enclosed is my resume for your review. I welcome the opportunity to discuss with you personally how my skills and strengths can best serve your company. I appreciate your time and consideration.

Sincerely,

Jan Ho

OTHER PORTFOLIO DOWNLOAD



ACHIEVEMENTS

· Company blog background and illustration

Design a series of background elements and illustrations for blogs; among them, the illustration design is drawn according to the content of the article and then sketched; Team communication and Design.

· eBook Cover Design

Ideation & develop new visual elements and illustration styles for the company, and create many company design materials for marketers for social media and advertising.

EDUCATION

Taipei PrivateTaibei High School 2000 Department of Art Design

Jinwen University of Science and Technology 2004 Department of Visual Communication Design

PERSONAL SKILLS

Photoshop	••••••
Illustrator	••••••
InDesign	••••••
Dreamweaver	••••••
Premiere	•••••
After Effects	•••••
HTML	•••••
CSS	••••••
Java Script	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$

WORK EXPERIENCE

2018 - 2020.9.11

Senior Graphic Designer

PORTFOLIO DOWNLOAD

Graphic design, explorations, illustrations, ideation; Event booth design and event collateral; Social media imagery for one-offs and campaigns; Digital marketing assets for advertising campaigns; Presentation creation for sales, events, and webinars; Editorial graphics/illustrations for blogs, both internal and external; Whitepaper and document creation; Email marketing newsletter design; Create blog header illustration; Infographics design

2017 - 2018

Produce Manager

Tawa Nevada Inc.

Recognize produce items, and obtain the basic product knowledge, including product categories, packing materials, storage temperature/methods, display Technics, seasonal products, etc. Implement feedback received from customer teams

and internal groups

2016 - 2017

Graphic Designer

PORTFOLIO DOWNLOAD

Tawa Supermarket Inc.

Design Stores Sign, Flyer, Poster, Banner. Daily emails, landing pages, homepage updates, promotions, display and affiliate marketing banners. Printing poster, sign, banner.

2015 - 2016

Graphic Designer

PORTFOLIO DOWNLOAD

EDI Media Inc.

Delegate tasks to the other members of the design team and provide counsel on all aspects of the project.

Work with creative and marketing teams to visualize, create, and execute marketing assets

2011 - 2015

Art Supervisor(Taiwan)

Online Technology

Manage Company Website and design game website, design event web pages, design ad banner.

Collaborates closely with all teams to create amazing graphics and digital composition while maintaining company brand standards

2010 - 2011

Network Director(Taiwan)

E-GO Internet Marketing

Plan and management activities with the project process.

2009 - 2010

Web Designer(Taiwan)

Iwplay World Interactive Entertainment Techno-

Design game's official website, game's visual image

website, event website, Flash, Banner, EDM, UI, CIS and photography.

Plan and control activities with the project process. Brand guidelines

2005 - 2009

Web Designer(Taiwan)

Metel Co., Ltd

Design game's official website, game's visual image website, event website, Flash, Banner, EDM, UI, CIS and photography.

Planning and control activities with the project process.

2004 - 2005

Web Designer(Taiwan)

Digital Kingstone Co., Ltd.

Design event website, Design EDM, Website update, Product photography.

COLLEAGUE RECOMMENDATIONS



Sean Clauretie (Head of design department)

I can only say nice things about Ian. He brought a genuine enthusiasm and willingness to problem solve to his position as Senior Designer at NS8. He is a reliable, organized, and talented designer on top of being an awesome person.

He brought his extensive international experience and cultural knowledge to his work, and would venture outside of his comfort zone to meet any challenge.



Arnold Dela Cruz (NS8 Creative Director)

Ian has been improving steadily in his role. Exploring and finding new and exciting visuals to add to the NS8 brand, Ian has become a "trendsetter" in our group. He exemplifies a can-do attitude and overcomes language barriers to deliver eye-catching designs that impress his peers.



Sam Hubbell (NS8 Senior Digital Designer)

Ian. You're such a talented creative. I actually used one of your designs to show a class i teach. Any company would be so lucky to have you on their team. Get Em while you can folks!



Jim Holborow (NS8 VP of Communications)

In my time as VP of Communications at NS8, Inc., Ian Ho served as a designer. We worked together very frequently on design and graphic assignments, including corporate presentations, social media graphics, sales enablement materials, trade show booths, case studies and other consumer-facing product materials. I have worked in advertising and marketing for 20 years, and I can say that Ian is among the best as a fast producer of work that hits the mark nearly every time on the first pass. He pays strict attention to specs, medium, and audience, and - what impressed me the most - was the creative interpretations he offered that stretched beyond the direction that was provided. He seemed to know what the project needed, even when I or other internal clients were not sure ourselves.

Thank You, Ian. You are a super talented and exceptionally kind human being. Let's please stay in touch. You were always there for me and for our work, and your creativity and your work has always been impressive and beyond expectation. Keep it up, sir



Ian Caramanzana (NS8 Content Marketer)

No matter what happens, you're my favorite Ian I've ever worked with. We did some great work together!

COLLEAGUE RECOMMENDATIONS



Philip Tortora (Communication Manager)

Ian is a superbly talented graphic designer who excels at creating assets and visuals for a wide range of business and marketing initiatives. From designing websites and interfaces, to creating a host of print and digital marketing assets, Ian is an elite designer who always brings flair and creativity to his work. The design skills and speed that Ian works with establish him as an extremely valuable team member in almost any creative environment. If you have a multitude of jobs that require the touch of an expert graphic designer, lan is somebody you should connect with.



Michael Hurley (NS8 Technical Product Manager)

Ian Ho was one of the first people I met at NS8. In addition to his unimpeachable design prowess, Ian is one of the most considerate, friendly and empathetic people I've met during my career. If you're looking for a talented graphic designer who is a joy to work with, reach out to my pal, lan!



Dave Jarrick (NS8 Executive VP of Human Resources)

Thank you Ian - the feeling has been very mutual

LETTER OF RECOMMENDATION



Arnold Dela Cruz (NS8 Creative Director)

I am pleased to write this letter of recommendation for Ian Ho. Ian worked as a graphic designer on my team from November 2019 to September 2020. During that period, Ian demonstrated a willingness to learn and improve as a designer. Mr. Ho tackled every assignment enthusiastically and always sought to clarify and understand the creative direction I provided.

lan's eye for visual design set microtrends within the department. Many of lan's design elements are visible in many marketing channel deliverables, including the company website, social media, digital ads, print media, and presentations. As creative director, I've even adapted some of lan's work into new iterations because they were visually impactful. With this in mind, I confidently recommend Ian for any role as a graphic designer.

Arnold Dela Cruz